Guide to the Robert M. Solow Papers, 1951-2011 and undated RL.01230
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, 1960-2013, 567352; 70 boxes
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1960-2013 and undated, 567400
    - 1997 Jul., 567570; 2 of 2 (Box 44)
      Mancur Olson. Statement "New Economic Policy for Russia."
    - 1997 Aug., 567569; 1 of 2 (Box 44)
    - 1997 Aug., 567568; 1 of 2 (Box 44)
      Partha Dasgupta, Olivier Blanchard.
    - 1997 Sep., 567567; 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      J.C.R. Dow on Macroeconomic Theory by Hahn and Solow. Response to comments on Solow's Tanner Lecture. Comment on Avinash Dixit and Mancur Olson. Correspondence with Martin N. Baily about outline for a JEP paper.
    - 1997 Sep., 567566; 2 of 3 (Box 45)
      Stuart W. Elliott.
    - 1997 Sep., 567565; 3 of 3 (Box 45)
      Volker Bohm.
    - 1997 Oct., 567564; 1 of 2 (Box 45)
      Bryan Ellickson, Herbert Grubel.
    - 1997 Oct., 567563; 2 of 2 (Box 45)
      Kofi Annan, Partha Dasgupta.
    - 1997 Nov., 567562; 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      Basil Moore.
    - 1997 Nov., 567561; 2 of 3 (Box 45)
      G.C. Harcourt, C.P. Kindleberger.
    - 1997 Nov., 567560; 3 of 3 (Box 45)
    - 1997 Dec., 567559; 1 of 3 (Box 46)
      Martin Weitzman.
    - 1997 Dec., 567558; 2 of 3 (Box 46)
      A reply to Frank Hahn on his paper on labor market flexibility and welfare.
    - 1997 Dec., 567557; 3 of 3 (Box 46)
    - 1998 Jan., 567556 (Box 46)
      A reply to Edward C. Prescott on his paper on TFP.
    - 1998 Feb., 567555; 1 of 2 (Box 46)
      Correspondence with Howard R. Vane about interview with Solow. A long mauscript of an interview with Solow.
    - 1998 Feb., 567554; 2 of 2 (Box 46)
      John T. Dunlop, Richard Startz, a reply to Pierre Levy on Fisher's ideas to the Phillips curve.
    - 1998 Mar., 567553; 1 of 2 (Box 46)
      Mancur Olson's death. Correspondence with Charles I. Jones on economies of scale.
    - 1998 Mar., 567552; 2 of 2 (Box 46)
    - 1998 Apr., 567551 (Box 47)
      Thomas J. Sargent.
    - 1998 May, 567550; 1 of 2 (Box 47)
      C.A.E. Goodhart, Thomas J. Sargent.
    - 1998 May, 567549; 2 of 2 (Box 47)
    - 1998 Jun., 567548; 1 of 2 (Box 47)
      Daniel Bell,Jean-Philippe Touffut.
    - 1998 Jun., 567547; 2 of 2 (Box 47)
      Comment on Robert C. Granger and his work on causality. Correspondence with Perry Mehrling on Social Security. Correspondence with Basil Moore on endogenous money supply.
    - 1998 Jul., 567546; 1 of 2 (Box 47)
      Kenneth J. Arrow, Richard A. Meese, Partha Dasgupta, Martin Weitzman.
    - 1998 Jul., 567545; 2 of 2 (Box 47)
      Robert J. Gordon. Comment on F.H. Hahn's "The "Exogenous" in "Endogenous" Growth Theory."
    - 1998 Aug., 567544; 1 of 2 (Box 48)
      F.H. Hahn, Basil Moore, James Tobin.
    - 1998 Aug., 567543; 2 of 2 (Box 48)
    - 1998 Sep., 567542 (Box 47)
      Olivier Blanchard, Daniel Bell.
    - 1998 Oct., 567541; 1 of 3 (Box 48)
      Correspondence with Ludger Lindlar on German unemployment. Exchange with Joachim Starbatty on Hayek and Asian crisis.
    - 1998 Oct., 567540; 2 of 3 (Box 48)
      John Moroney, Jeremy Stone.
    - 1998 Oct., 567539; 3 of 3 (Box 48)
    - 1998 Nov., 567538; 1 of 2 (Box 48)
      Assessment of Robert Hall. Exchange with Alan Kruger on JEP.
    - 1998 Nov., 567537; 2 of 2 (Box 48)
      Michael Meeropol.
    - 1998 Dec., 567536; 1 of 3 (Box 48)
      A reply to Charles R. Hulten on his TFP survey.
    - 1998 Dec., 567535; 2 of 3 (Box 49)
      M. Ali Khan on Georgescu-Roegen.
    - 1998 Dec., 567534; 3 of 3 (Box 49)
      Mark Prell.
    - 1999 Jan., 567533 (Box 49)
      Albert Hirschmann. Maurice Scott. Letter to Olivier Blanchard about Peter Diamond. Letter to Albert Hunt comparing different chairmans of the Fed. Manuscript of the review of "The Crisis of Global Capitalism" by George Soros.
    - 1999 Feb., 567532; 1 of 2 (Box 49)
      Stanley Fischer, Eric Wanner on macroeconomic policy management.
    - 1999 Feb., 567531; 2 of 2 (Box 49)
      P.K. Seidman.
    - 1999 Mar., 567530; 1 of 2 (Box 49)
      Richard R. Nelson.
    - 1999 Mar., 567529; 2 of 2 (Box 49)
    - 1999 Apr., 567528; 1 of 2 (Box 49)
      Hans G. Danielmeyer, Dale W. Jorgenson, a copy of an old letter from Joan Robinson to R.S. Eckaus in 1955.
    - 1999 Apr., 567527; 2 of 2 (Box 50)
      Letter to Daniel Bell on advances and failures of technology. Letter to Tibor Sctitovsky on a case study of a BMW factory. Letter to Olivier Blanchard on Blanchard's paper on shocks and institutions as explanatory variables of the European unemployment.
    - 1999 May, 567526; 1 of 2 (Box 50)
      Philippe Aghion, Jack M. Hollander. Exchange with Richard Halpern on Solow's review of a book by Soros. Letter to Olivier Blanchard about a Center for the Study of Economic Growth. An exchange with Horace Gaims on monetary reform.
    - 1999 May, 567525; 2 of 2 (Box 50)
      Letter to Timothy Bartik on elasticity of demand for labor.
    - 1999 Jun., 567524; 1 of 2 (Box 50)
      Robert Gordon. Letter on Xavier Ragot's paper on division of labor. Assessment of Partha Dasgupta. Letter to David Altig on SOcial Security. Letter to Olivier Blanchard on VARs.
    - 1999 Jun., 567523; 2 of 2 (Box 50)
      Daron Acemoglu.
    - 1999 Jul., 567522; 1 of 2 (Box 50)
      Letter to Sanford D. Gordon on economists with Jewish background. Letter to George Tavlas on Milton Friedman. Letter to Samuel Bowles and Herbert Gintis on the role of institutions in transition economies. Letter to Jose Villacis on German Bernacer.
    - 1999 Jul., 567521; 2 of 2 (Box 50)
      The Nobel Foundation.
    - 1999 Aug., 567520; 1 of 2 (Box 50)
      Charles Plott, Howard R. Vane. Exchange with Frank H. Hahn on expectations. Answers to questions related to factors of U.S. economic growth, trade barriers, the theory of endogenous growth, or dollarization.
    - 1999 Aug., 567519; 2 of 2 (Box 50)
    - 1999 Sep., 567518 (Box 51)
      Olivier Blanchard, Frank H. Hahn, Charles Plott. Letter to M. Vincent Courtilot on important French economists. Charles Steindel on current business cycle. A short remebrance on his position at CEA.
    - 1999 Oct., 567517; 1 of 2 (Box 51)
      Victor E. Ferrall, Jr. Letter to Robert J. Barbera on monetary policy.
    - 1999 Oct., 567516; 2 of 2 (Box 51)
      Letter to Jerald Hage on the process of innovation.
    - 1999 Nov., 567515 (Box 51)
    - 1999 Dec., 567514; 1 of 2 (Box 51)
      William Easterly, Frank H. Hahn. Letter to Alan Peacock on homo economicus.
    - 1999 Dec., 567513; 2 of 2 (Box 51)
      Olivier Blanchard. Letter to John Leahy on the social discount rate.
    - 2000 Jan. 6-Jan. 9, 567512 (Box 89)
      William A. Barnett.
    - 2000 Jan. 18-Mar. 6, 567511 (Box 89)
      Robert J. Gordon, Lawrence Ball.
    - 2000 Mar. 6 18-Mar. 14, 567510 (Box 89)
      Amit Bhaduri.
    - 2000 Mar. 14 18-Apr. 5, 567509 (Box 89)
      Kaushik Basu, Benigno Valdes.
    - 2000 Apr. 5 18-Apr. 17, 567508 (Box 89)
      Roger Backhouse, Orley Ashenfelter.
    - 2000 Apr. 20-May 9, 567507 (Box 89)
      Robert W. Fogel, Olivier Blanchard
    - 2000 May 9-May 30, 567506 (Box 90)
      Thomas Palley, A.P. Thirlwall
    - 2000 Jun. 1-Jun. 27, 567505 (Box 90)
      Partha Dasgupta, David F. Weiman.
    - 2000 Jul. 5-Aug. 1, 567504 (Box 90)
      Eli Schwartz, Hirofumi Uzawa, Daniel Bell.
    - 2000 Aug. 1-Aug. 21, 567503 (Box 90)
      David F. Weiman, Jeffrey Williamson.
    - 2000 Aug. 21-Aug. 30, 567502 (Box 90)
    - 2000 Aug. 30-Oct. 3, 567501 (Box 90)
      Harold T. Shapiro.
    - 2000 Oct. 3-Oct. 15, 567500 (Box 91)
    - 2000 Oct. 16-Oct. 24, 567499 (Box 91)
    - 2000 Oct. 24-Nov. 13, 567498 (Box 91)
    - 2000 Nov. 14-Nov. 27, 567497 (Box 91)
      W.W. Rostow.
    - 2000 Nov. 28-Dec. 18, 567496 (Box 91)
      Jean Tirole, Olivier Blanchard.
    - 2000 Dec. 18-Dec. 28, 567495 (Box 91)
      Jean Tirole.
    - 2001 Jan. 5-Feb. 2, 567494 (Box 91)
    - 2001 Feb. 8-Feb. 20, 567493 (Box 92)
      Daniel Bell, Alan Krueger.
    - 2001 Feb. 21-Mar. 23, 567492 (Box 92)
      Oliver Williamson, Lawrence Ball, Paul A. Samuelson, David H. Cohen.
    - 2001 Mar. 23-Mar. 27, 567491 (Box 92)
      Carl Campbell.
    - 2001 Apr. 3-Apr. 10, 567490 (Box 92)
      Assar Lindbeck on welfare state, Olivier Blancard, Daniel Bell, Frank Hahn.
    - 2001 Apr. 11-May 9, 567489 (Box 92)
      Olivier Blanchard, Luigi Pasinetti.
    - 2001 May 9-Jun. 17, 567488 (Box 92)
      Luigi Pasinetti, Stanley Fischer, Robert Dorfman, Martin Weitzman, Ben Bernake.
    - 2001 Jun. 17-Aug. 1, 567487 (Box 93)
      Luigi Pasinetti, Andrew R. Solow, Olivier Blanchard.
    - 2001 Aug. 1-Aug. 28, 567486 (Box 93)
    - 2001 Sep. 5-Sep. 17, 567485 (Box 93)
      Sander M. Levin, Alexander Ryzhenkov.
    - 2001 Sep. 17-Oct. 4, 567484 (Box 93)
    - 2001 Oct. 4-Oct. 22, 567483 (Box 93)
    - 2001 Oct. 22-Nov. 19, 567482 (Box 93)
      Diego Comin, Edward C. Prescott, Douglas Gale.
    - 2001 Nov. 23- Dec. 20, 567481 (Box 94)
      Xavier Gabaix, George A. Akerlof, Partha Dasgupta, Thomas Sargent.
    - 2002 Jan. 9-Jan. 23, 567480 (Box 94)
    - 2002 Jan. 23-Mar. 6, 567479 (Box 94)
      Pham Hoang Van.
    - 2002 Mar. 6-Apr. 2, 567478 (Box 94)
    - 2002 Apr. 2-May 17, 567477 (Box 94)
      Paul Samuelson.
    - 2002 May 20-Jun. 13, 567476 (Box 94)
      Sharon Harrison.
    - 2002 Jun. 14-Jul. 15, 567475 (Box 94)
      David Warsh.
    - 2002 Jul. 15-Aug. 20, 567474 (Box 95)
      David Warsh, Mark Blaug.
    - 2002 Aug. 22-Sep. 24, 567473 (Box 95)
      M. Jean-Philippe Touffut, Bert Hickman.
    - 2002 Sep. 24-Oct. 17, 567472 (Box 95)
      Cristine Levenduski, Eric Wanner, Frank Newman.
    - 2002 Oct. 23- Oct. 30, 567471 (Box 95)
      Frank N. Newman.
    - 2002 Nov. 7-Nov. 21, 567470 (Box 95)
      Frank N. Newman, Thomas J. Sargent, Frederic S. Mishkin.
    - 2002 Nov. 26-Dec. 11, 567469 (Box 95)
      Frank N. Newman, John Hartwick, Nancy Weinberg.
    - 2002 Dec. 12-Dec. 23, 567468 (Box 96)
      Laurence Ball, Gregory Mankiw, Frank N. Newman, George Soros.
    - 2003 Jan. 8-Jan. 23, 567467 (Box 96)
      George Soros.
    - 2003 Jan. 23-Mar. 4, 567466 (Box 96)
      Laurence Ball, Bert G. Hickman, Janos Kornai. Letter to Edward A. Malloy on heterodox economics.
    - 2003 Mar. 4-Apr. 23, 567465 (Box 96)
      Franklin M. Fisher, George Soros, Oliver Williamson.
    - 2003 Apr. 23-Jun. 4, 567464 (Box 96)
      Letter to Jonas Frycklund on EMU.
    - 2003 Jun. 4-Jun. 26, 567463 (Box 96)
      Bjorn Lomborg.
    - 2003 Jul. 1-Jul. 15, 567462 (Box 97)
      Mark Blyth, Charles I. Jones, William Lewis.
    - 2003 Jul. 21- Sep. 2, 567461 (Box 97)
      Olivier de La Grandville, J.R. Sargebt.
    - 2003 Sep. 3-Oct. 6, 567460 (Box 97)
      Karl Shell, Michael Kaser.
    - 2003 Oct. 6- Oct. 29, 567459 (Box 97)
      Olivier de La Grandville.
    - 2003 Nov. 3- Nov.20, 567458 (Box 97)
      Bengt Holmstrom, Partha Dasgupta, a report prepared by Kenneth Arrow, Gary Becker, Dennis Carlton and Robert Solow on behalf of Verizon on telecommunications.
    - 2003 Nov. 21- Dec. 29, 567457 (Box 97)
      Robert Chirinko, Athanasios Orphanides.
    - 2004 Jan. 2- Feb. 4, 567456 (Box 98)
      Ross M. Stard.
    - 2004 Feb. 11-Mar. 18, 567455 (Box 98)
      Orley Ahenfrelter, Avinash Dixit, Arnold Kling. Letter to Marc-Andre Bacon on Sidney Siegel. Letter to Alexander J. Field on Mirowski.
    - 2004 Mar. 22-May 4, 567454 (Box 98)
      Avinash K. Dixit, Jordi Gali, Oliver de La Grandville, Janos Kornai, Bjorn Lomborg, Martin Weitzman.
    - 2004 May 4-Jun. 15, 567453 (Box 98)
      Francis M. Bator, Perry Mehrling.
    - 2004 Jun. 16-Aug. 2, 567452 (Box 98)
      Partha Dasgupta, William Easterly, Robert E. Lucas Jr., Edmund S. Phelps. Letter to Roger Backhouse on 1968 QJE paper.
    - 2004 Aug. 2-31, 567451 (Box 99)
      Luigi Pasinetti, Peter Englund, Partha Dasgupta.
    - 2004 Sep. 9- Oct. 29, 567450 (Box 99)
    - 2004 Oct. 29- Nov. 29, 567449 (Box 99)
      Jean-Philippe Touffut, a letter to Samuel Brittan on Keynes and Keynesian economics, Daniel Schiffman, Olivier de La Grandville.
    - 2004 Nov. 29- Dec. 23, 567448 (Box 99)
      Martin Weitzman, James Heckman.
    - 2005 Jan. 10- Feb. 14, 567447 (Box 99)
      Partha Dasgupta, Roger Backhouse.
    - 2005 Feb. 14- Mar. 14, 567446 (Box 99)
      John Hartwick, Assar Lindbeck.
    - 2005 Mar. 17- Apr. 13, 567445 (Box 100)
      Partha Dasgupta, Olivier de La Grandville. A support letter for Jean-Paul Fitoussi.
    - 2005 Apr. 16-May 26, 567444 (Box 100)
      Alan S. Blinder, David Colander, Olivier de La Grandville, Janos Kornai.
    - 2005 May 30-Jul. 18, 567443 (Box 100)
      David Colander, Olivier de La Grandville, Frank Newman.
    - 2005 Jul. 18-Aug. 15, 567442 (Box 100)
    - 2005 Aug. 15-Oct. 3, 567441 (Box 100)
      Olivier Blanchard, Olivier de La Grandvillei. Discussion with Jagdish Bhagwati on Nobel Prizes.
    - 2005 Oct. 3-Nov. 28, 567440 (Box 100)
      Alan S. Blinder, Olivier de La Grandvillei, Janos Kornai, Ian McDonald.
    - 2005 Nov. 28- Dec. 19, 567439 (Box 101)
      Herbert Giersch, Daron Acemoglu.
    - 2005 Dec. 19-27, 567438 (Box 101)
      Vijay Joshi, Jacques-Henri David, Avinash K. Dixit, Desiree Desierto, Olivier de La Grandville.
    - 2006 Jan. 3- Feb. 22, 567437 (Box 101)
      Peter Englund,Olivier de La Grandville.
    - 2006 Feb. 28- Mar. 21, 567436 (Box 101)
      Guillermina Jasso.
    - 2006 Mar. 21- May 2, 567435 (Box 101)
      Peter McAdam, Paul Krugman, Edmond Malinavud, Olivier de La Grandville.
    - 2006 May 2- Jun. 6, 567434 (Box 101)
      Peter McAdam, Olivier de La Grandville.
    - 2006 Jul. 5- Aug. 16, 567433 (Box 102)
      Peter McAdam, Edmond Malinvaud.
    - 2006 Aug. 27- Oct. 18, 567432 (Box 102)
      N. Gregory Mankiw, Gustavo Piga.
    - 2006 Oct. 18-24, 567431 (Box 102)
      Robert S. Goldfarb, Ian McDonald, John B. Hall.
    - 2006 Nov. 2- Dec. 7, 567430 (Box 102)
      Jean Tirole, Martin Weitzman.
    - 2006 Dec. 14-2007 Jan. 31, 567429 (Box 102)
      Peter McAdam.
    - 2007 Feb. 13-Apr. 12, 567428 (Box 102)
      Jean-Philippe Touffut, Peter Diamond, Stephen Stigler.
    - 2007 May 3-Jul. 23, 567427 (Box 103)
      Benjamin M. Friedman.
    - 2007 Jul. 23-Sep. 20, 567426 (Box 103)
      Joel Moses, Michael Spence.
    - 2007 Sep. 24-Oct. 27, 567425 (Box 103)
      Ian McDonald, Olivier de La Grandville, Luigi Pasinetti.
    - 2007 Nov. 3-Dec. 19, 567424 (Box 103)
      Johathan Schlefer.
    - 2007 Dec. 20- 2008 Jan. 23, 567423 (Box 103)
      Jean-Philippe Touffut, Luigi Pasinetti.
    - 2008 Jan. 28- Feb. 26, 567422 (Box 104)
      Dagobert L. Brito, Robert U. Ayres.
    - 2008 Mar. 11-May 13, 567421 (Box 104)
      Robert U. Ayres, Luigi Pasinetti.
    - 2008 May 13-Jun. 19, 567420 (Box 104)
      Jacob Hacker.
    - 2008 Jun. 25-Aug. 14, 567419 (Box 104)
      Janice Marray, Marion Sandler.
    - 2008 Aug. 14-Sep. 18, 567418 (Box 104)
      Scott Carter, Niels Kemper, Paul Joskow.
    - 2008 Sep. 18-Oct. 28, 567417 (Box 104)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, Eric Wanner.
    - 2008 Oct. 28-Dec. 31, 567416 (Box 105)
      Axel Leijonhufvud, E. Roy Weintraub.
    - 2008 Dec. 31, 567415 (Box 105)
      Francis M. Bator, Hans-Werner Sinn, Benjamin M. Friedman.
    - 2009 Jan. 5-27, 567414 (Box 105)
    - 2009 Jan. 27-May 11, 567413 (Box 105)
      Giulio Pontecorvo, Dimitris Kyriakou, Peter McAdam.
    - 2009 May 11-26, 567412 (Box 105)
      Axel Leijonhufvud, Avinash K. Dixit.
    - 2009 May 27-Jul. 8, 567411 (Box 105)
      Lefteris Tsoulfidis, Partha Dasgupta.
    - 2009 Jul. 8-Aug. 18, 567410 (Box 106)
      Partha Dasgupta, Ian McDonald.
    - 2009 Aug. 18-Oct. 16, 567409 (Box 106)
      Robert Goldfarb, Janos Kornai.
    - 2009 Oct. 16-Nov. 29, 567408 (Box 106)
      George Akerlof, Kenneth J. Arrow. Exchange with Max Corden on Ben Bernanke and the MIT tradition.
    - 2009 Nov. 24-Dec. 28, 567407 (Box 106)
      Kenneth J. Arrow, Janos Kornai.
    - 2010 Jan. 7-Feb. 2, 567406 (Box 106)
      Stanislav Burdein, Daniel Xif.
    - 2010 Feb. 25-Apr. 21, 567405 (Box 106)
      George Akerlof, Olivier de La Grandville, George Waldstein, Carl Christian von Weizsaecker.
    - 2010 Apr. 22-Jun. 23, 567404 (Box 107)
      Roger Backhouse, Gordon Berlin, Jagdish Bhagwati, Alan Blinder, Pierre-Andre de Chalendar, Avinash K. Dixit, Benjamin Friedman, Olivier de La Grandville, Robert Hall, Tom Killian, Ian M. McDonald, Mark Schneider.
    - 2010 Jul. 1-Sep. 9, 567403 (Box 107)
      Horst Albach, E. Roy Weintraub. Correspondence with Sidney Winter on DSGE.
    - 2010 Sep. 16-2011 Feb. 1, 567402 (Box 107)
      Nomination of Peter Diamond to the Board of Governors.
    - 2010 Oct. 4-Nov. 30, 838058 (Box 110)
    - 2010 Dec. 1-2011 Apr. 11, 838059 (Box 110)
    - 2011 Jun. 6-Nov. 5, 838060 (Box 110)
    - 2011 Nov. 12-Dec. 29, 838061 (Box 110)
    - 2012 Jan. 2-Sept. 28, 838062 (Box 110)
    - 2012 Oct. 2-2013 Apr. 9, 838063 (Box 110)
    - 2013 May 4-July 24, 838064 (Box 110)
    - 2013 Aug. 6- Oct. 19, 838065 (Box 110)
    - undated, 838066 (Box 110)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence, 567356
    Correspondence loosely arranged by last name. Notable names are listed below.
    - A, 567399; 3 folders (Box 52)
      Kenneth J. Arrow, George A. Akerlof, Richard Auster, and AEA.
    - B, 567398; Folders 1-5 of 7 (Box 52)
      Jagdish Bhagwati, William J. Baumol, Edwin Burmeister, Theodore W. Schultz, Daniel Bell, Edwin Burmeister, Gary S. Becker, Christopher Bliss,D.M. Bensusuan-Butt, G.L. Bach.
    - B, 567397; Folders 6-7 of 7 (Box 53)
      Martin J. Bailey, William J Baumol, Martin Beckmann,Frank Brechling, Hans Brems, O.H. Brownlee, Susan Burch, G.L. Bach.
    - C, 567396 (Box 53)
      Committee for Economic Development.
    - C, 567395 (Box 53)
      Council of Economic Advisors.
    - C, 567394 (Box 53)
    - C, 567393; Folders 1-4 of 4 (Box 53)
      Carl F. Christ, James S. Coleman, Gregory C. Chow, John R. Coleman.
    - D, 567392; Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box 53)
      Christopher Dougherty, Herman E. Daly, John S. Dyson, Edward Denison, Romensh K. Diwan, Robert Dorfman, Peter Diamond, Evsey D. Domar.
    - D, 567391; Folders 3-4 of 4 (Box 54)
      P.N. Dhar, Phoebus Dhrymes, Thomas F. Dernburg, Gerard Debreu, Evsey D. Domar, Robert Dorfman.
    - E, 567390; Folders 1-2 of 2 (Box 54)
      William K. Estes, Otto Eckstein, Robert Eisner.
    - E, 567389; Folders 1-2 of 2 (Box 54)
      Econometrica.
    - E, 567388; Folders 1-4 of 5 (Box 54)
      Econometri Soceity.
    - E, 567387; Folders 5 of 5 (Box 55)
    - E, 567386; Folders 1-3 of 3 (Box 55)
      Engagements: Berkeley Research Program, Data Processing Management Association, Conference on Research in Income and Wealth.
    - F, 567385; Folders 1-3 of 3 (Box 55)
      Charles E. Ferguson, Robert W. Fogel, F.M. Fisher, Milton Friedman, William Fellner, David Fand, Ragnar Frisch.
    - G, 567384; Folders 1-3 of 3 (Box 55)
      Zvi Griliches, J.K. Galbraith, H.A. John Green, W.M. Gorman, R.A. Gordon, David Gale, Harry Grubert.
    - H, 567383; Folders 1-3 of 3 (Box 55)
      Gottfried Haberler,Frank Hahn,Bernard F. Haley, George A. Hay, Richard Heflebower,I.N. Herstein, Charles Hitch, Roy Harrod.
    - H, 567382 (Box 56)
      John Hicks.
    - H, 567381; Folders 1-6 of 6 (Box 56)
      Holden Day.
    - I, 567380 (Box 56)
      Ken-ichi Inada.
    - J, 567379; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 56)
      Dale Jorgenson, Harry G. Johnson.
    - J, 567378; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 57)
      Harry G. Johnson,Peter Jay.
    - K, 567377; Folders 1-4 of 4 (Box 57)
      Nicholas Kaldor,T.C. Koopmans, Lawrence R. Klein, Murray C. Kemp, T.N. Krishnan, Irving Kristol.
    - L, 567376; Folders 1-2 of 2 (Box 57)
      Richard Lipsey, Robert Lucas, Wassily W. Leontief, H.G. Lewis.
    - M, 567375; Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box 57)
      Lionel W. McKenzie, Franco Modigliani, Ronald I. McKinon, James Mirrless.
    - M, 567374; Folders 3-4 of 4 (Box 58)
      Lionel W. McKenziem James Mirrless.
    - N, 567373; Folders 1-2 of 2 (Box 58)
      Keizo Nagatani, Edward Nell, Douglas C. North.
    - N, 567372 (Box 58)
      National Bureau of Economic Research.
    - N, 567371; Folders 1-4 of 4 (Box 58)
      National Commission on Techonology Automation and Economic Progress.
    - O, 567370 (Box 58)
      Saburo Okita.
    - P, 567369; Folders 1-3 of 3 (Box 59)
      Luigi Pasinetti, Don Patinkin, Edmund S. Phelps, Robert Pollak.
    - Q, 567368 (Box 58)
      Richard E. Quandt.
    - R, 567367; Folders 1-3 of 3 (Box 59)
      Joan Robinson,Richard Ruggles.
    - R, 567366; Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box 59)
      Rand Corporation.
    - R, 567365; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 60)
    - S, 567364; Folders 1-7 of 7 (Box 60)
      George J. Stigler, Joseph E. Stiglitz, Sidney Siegel,Herbert A. Simon, Robert H. Strotz, Alan Sweezy, J.R. Sargent.
    - S, 567363 (Box 60)
      Secretary of Treasury Panel of Advisors.
    - T, 567362; Folders 1-2 of 2 (Box 61)
      James Tobin, Jan Tinbergen, Donald P. Tucker.
    - U, 567361 (Box 61)
      Hirofumi Uzawa, Pierre Uri.
    - V, 567360 (Box 61)
      Stephen Viederman.
    - W, 567359; Folders 1-5 of 5 (Box 61)
      Henry Y. Wan, Jr.,Leon Wegge, Fried M. Westfield, Herman Wold.
    - Y, 567358; Folders 1-2 of 2 (Box 61)
      Joel Yellin.
    - Z, 567357 (Box 61)
      Giovanni Zanetti.
  - Alphabetical Correspondence (Recommendations), 1971-1986, 567353
    Alphabetical correspondence regarding recommendations. May contain information that is covered by privacy and confidentiality laws; publication or distribution is prohibited without consent of subject.
    - A-L, 567355 (Box 62)
    - M-Z, 567354 (Box 63)
- Teaching Materials, 1969-1996 and undated, 567343; 6 boxes
  Includes the teaching materials used in Solow's courses, spanning much of his 40-year MIT career, as well as the notes and materials used for lectures given at other forums and institutions of higher learning. Materials consist of reading lists, syllabi, outlines, exams, problem sets and their solutions, homework, waivers, attendance rosters, assignments, spiral notebooks of economic equations, and personal preparatory notes handwritten by Solow. Arranged in order as received.
  - 1980s-1996, 567351 (Box 64)
  - 1976-1992, 567350 (Box 65)
  - 1972-1975, 567349 (Box 66)
  - 1969-1973, 567348 (Box 67)
  - Miscellaneous dates and undated, 567347 (Box 68)
  - Primarily undated, 567346 (Box 69)
  - 1982-1985, 567345 (Box 88)
  - Matsui lecture notes, 1985, 567344 (Box 88)
- Published Papers and Writings, 1951-2011, 567332; 10 boxes
  Includes most of Solow's major publications and co-publications (see bibliography for the few exceptions). These include his Ph. D. thesis, speeches, lectures, invited lectures, panel discussions, op-ed pieces, journal articles, brochures, pamphlets, reviews of his works and his responses to said reviews, congressional testimony, and memorial tributes, as well as the rough drafts and/or notes for these documents.
  - 1951-1965; bibliography, 567342 (Box 70)
  - 1966-1971, 567341 (Box 71)
  - 1972-1977, 567340 (Box 72)
  - 1978-1984, 567339 (Box 73)
  - 1985-1990, 567338 (Box 74)
  - 1991-1996, 567337 (Box 75)
  - 1996-2000, 567336 (Box 76)
  - 2001-2005, 567335 (Box 77)
  - 2006-2013, 567334 (Box 108)
  - Undated, 838067 (Box 111)
  - 1984-1999; oversized periodicals - reviews, 567333 (Box 78)
- Professional Service Series, 1961-1986, 567303; 9 boxes
  Includes varied documents associated with the groups Robert Solow was either a member of, held a position in, wrote pieces for, or supported. These documents include: correspondence, meeting minutes, proposals, reports, publications, votes, elections, and financial reports. The largest organizations represented in this series are the American Economic Association, the National Bureau of Economic Research, and the Institute for Advanced Study at Princeton.
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Urban Studies, 567331; 5 folders (Box 79)